<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on DevBlog</title>
    
    
    
    <link>https://metekarasakal.me/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on DevBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://metekarasakal.me/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Positive Tree In Haskell</title>
      <link>https://metekarasakal.me/blog/posts/recursive-positivetree-in-hs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metekarasakal.me/blog/posts/recursive-positivetree-in-hs/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Introduction 🌲 This is a project builds positive tree by adding/multiplying elements in pairs from bottom to top and there are functions that I will be mentioning later. This project can be educative for people who are starting or currently using functional PL&amp;rsquo;s. I need to mention that this is an assignment done for a course in METU NCC. You can check full code here.
Table of contents  Preperation Construct The Tree Generate Height of the Tree Find the Weight of a Level in Tree Manual Traversal After Finding Declared Node Conclusion  Preperation Firstly I needed a custom Tree data type.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What topics will be included in this blog?</title>
      <link>https://metekarasakal.me/blog/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 21:05:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metekarasakal.me/blog/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          What is DevBlog and Why did I create this blog? Firstly, I would like to mention what I meant by saying that it is a dev blog it usually has one meaning which is software development blog, but in my case it has another meaning &amp;ldquo;self-development blog&amp;rdquo;, because I am still a young person to call myself a Software Developer or Computer Engineer, however I still can build my own projects and develop my knowledge, that is exactly why I was looking for a way to deploy this blog on &amp;ldquo;/blog&amp;rdquo; slug for 1 whole day.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>